serverpoint.com 2019-07-05

# Privacy Policy

                                      Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important for A+ Hosting Inc. DBA ServerPoint.Com (“the Company”
“ServerPoint”). We collect the minimum amount of information about you that is
commensurate with providing you with a satisfactory service. Your information is never sold
or shared with any company not related to ServerPoint.com.
Credit card information is of course shared with our credit card processor in order to charge
your credit card.
We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and
security. This Privacy Policy describes how the Company collects information from all end
users of the Company's Internet services (the "Services") — those who access some of our
Services but do not have accounts ("Visitors") as well as those who pay a service fee to
subscribe to the Service ("Customers") — what we do with the information we collect, and
the choices Visitors and Customers have concerning the collection and use of such
information. The Company requests that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.
Introduction
The Company is in the business of web hosting, not marketing. We use you personal data for internal
purposes only, contact information, billing information, technical information, usage information and
reseller information. The use of this information is mainly to assure quality service for our customers, and
of course collect payment. On the other hand, visitor information is also use for internal purposes only.
We conduct research with this data to improve our marketing strategy. In addition, we will not use any of
this information to sell data or spam users, customers or visitors. The Company also stores all
correspondence between us and our customers for record keeping and historical service reference. The
Company does engage computer tracking with the SOLE purpose of identifying illegal usage or fraudulent
behavior of some individuals or organizations that may be trying to operate or are in operations on our
servers.
Registration
Customers are asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Services including
name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), and the type of
personal computer being used to access the Services. The personal information collected from Customers
during the registration process is used to manage each Member's account (such as for billing purposes).
This information is not shared with third parties, unless specifically stated otherwise or in special
circumstances. However, in instances where the Company and a partner (or affiliate) jointly promote the
Services, the Company may provide the partner certain personal information, such as the name, address,
and username of persons who subscribed to the Services as a result of the joint promotion for the sole
purpose of allowing us and the partner to assess the results of the promotion. The Company may also
generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information Customers provide during

registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of Customers). As explained in more detail
below, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to sell advertisements that appear on
the Services.
After you have signed up for our Services, we may be in communication with you about your account,
technical questions you may have about the Services, or any other matter relating to the Services. These
communications are essential to our relationship with you and to our ability to provide you with quality
Services that are responsive to your needs. As a result, we may maintain information about our
communications with you for future use.
Domain Registration
Domain name registration information legally has to be available to the public. Since domain name
registration information is available to the public, anyone can access it through “WHOIS” searches. The
WHOIS database is a publicly accessible database that lists the domain name and contact information of
each registrant. The domain name registration you provide is hosted by us to the public. At times our
customers may have been included within searches of the WHOIS database. However, the SPAM they
receive does not in any way come from the Company.
The Company Partners and Sponsors
Some the Company products and services are offered to Visitors and Customers in conjunction with a
non-affiliated partner. To provide Visitors and Customers some of these products and services, the
partner may need to collect and maintain personal information. In these instances, we will provide such
data collected or transferred to our Partners and Sponsors (e.g., domain registration). Additionally, many
the Company Customers have co-branded pages that are co-sponsored by non-affiliated partners. The
Company will share non-identifying and aggregate information (except as described above), but not
personal information, with such partners in order to administer the co-branded products or services
offered.
Online Shopping
At some Web sites, you can purchase products and services or register to receive materials, such as a
catalog or new product and service updates. In many cases, you may be asked to provide contact
information, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and credit/debit card
information. If you complete an order for someone else, such as an online gift order sent directly to a
recipient, you may be asked to provide information about the recipient, such as the recipient's name,
address, and phone number. The Company has no control over the third parties' use of any personal
information you provide when placing such an order. Please exercise care when doing so. If you order
products directly from the Company, we will use the personal information you provide only to process

that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to
complete that order.
Online Advertisements
The Company displays our online advertisements. We share aggregated and non-identifying information
about our Visitors and Customers collected through the registration process as well as through online
surveys and promotions with these advertisers. Additionally, in some instances, we use this aggregated
and non-identifying information to deliver tailored advertisements. For instance, an advertiser tells us the
audience they want to reach and provides us an advertisement tailored to the audience. Based upon the
aggregated and non-identifying information we have collected, we may then display the advertisement to
the intended audience. The Company does not share personal information about its Visitors or Customers
with these advertisers.
Our Web site may allow for a chat function. Chat functions allow you to participate in "live" online
conversations with us on our Web site. Although the transcripts from the chats may be stored internally
on in-house servers for our records only, we collect no personally identifiable information about you when
you participate unless you choose to provide that information to us.
The basic user information collected is used to help us analyze Web traffic, improve the content of our
Web site and improve your experience on our Web site. We do not trade, rent or sell your personal
information to others, except as detailed in this Policy.
Responses to Email Inquiries
When Visitors or Customers send email inquiries to the Company, the return email address is used to
answer the email inquiry we receive. The Company does not use the return email address for any other
purpose and does not share the return email address with any third party.
Voluntary Customer Surveys
We may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. We encourage our customers
to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information that helps us to
improve the types of services we offer and how we provide them to you. Your personal information and
responses will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation
in our customer surveys is voluntary. We take the information we receive from individuals responding to
our Customer Surveys and combine (or aggregate) it with the responses of other the Company customers
to create broader, generic responses to the survey questions. We then use the aggregated information to
improve the quality of our services to you, and to develop new services and products. This aggregated,
non-personally identifying information may be shared with third parties.

Special Cases
It is the Company's policy not to use or share the personal information about Visitors of Customers in ways
unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise
prohibit such unrelated uses. However, the Company may disclose personal information about Visitors or
Customers, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services,
for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including: to satisfy
laws, such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests
for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action
against someone who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or other user policies; to operate the
Services properly; or to protect the Company and our Customers.
"Cookies" and How the Company Uses Them
We may at times use cookies, which are small pieces of information that a Web site can store in a
designated file on your computer. Cookies allow a Web application to respond to you as an individual. By
gathering and remembering information about your preferences, the Web application can tailor its
operation to your needs, likes, and dislikes. Most web browsers allow you to control this use of cookies.
Please take a look at your particular browser for instructions on this function. If you elect to disable
cookies, please keep in mind that you will not be able to take full advantage of a personalized experience
on our Web site. It is possible that some portions of the site will not function properly or may perform
more slowly if you choose to reject cookies.
Statistics
We use information gathered about you from our site statistics to help diagnose problems with our server,
and to administer our Web site. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us
improve our site and make your browsing and purchasing experience more enjoyable. This is not linked to
any personally identifiable information, except as necessary to prevent fraud or abuse on our system.
The Company's Commitment to Children's Privacy
Protecting children's privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children's
Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. While we make every effort to ensure
that these Web sites are fun and age-appropriate for our younger audience, we believe that there is no
substitute for proper parental supervision. The Company recommends that children ask a parent for
permission before sending personal information to the Company, or to anyone else online.

The Company does not sell products or services for purchase by children. Customers must be at least 18
years of age to sign up for our services.
Public Forums
Please remember that any information you may disclose in blog, or other public areas of our Web sites or
the Internet (ex. our social media account), becomes public information. You should exercise caution
when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas.
The Company's Commitment to Data Security
Services and Web sites we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and
alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and
security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent
third-party "hackers" from illegally obtaining this information.
How to Access or Modify Your Information
The Company offers Customers the opportunity to access or modify information provided during
registration. To access or modify such information login into your Client Portal or contact our staff via the
ticket system for specific instructions on how to do it.
Where to Direct Questions About the Company's Privacy Policy
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you want to know what information we have
collected about you, please contact our Customer Service Department.
Exceptions
The Company is not responsible for the personal data collected by web sites and companies hosted on our
servers.
As stated previously in this policy, we will never give out your information without your permission. The
only exceptions to this are, by the authority of the law, in the good-faith belief that such action is
necessary in order to conform to the law, or we must comply with a legal process served on our web site.
We may also need to give out your information if one of our partners requires it, but these situations are
rare and we will always ask for your explicit permission first.
By the authority of law means that if for any reason in an investigation by the United States Federal
Government (e. i. Federal Bureau of Investigations, Internal Revenue Service, US Department of Defense,

US Department of Justice and the such) or by the order any United States and/or State Court that would
subpoena that information, the information will be disclosed to the appropriate authorities. All in
accordance to US Federal Law and State law depending on the customer's original jurisdiction. The
Company will abide by any legislation, past and future, regarding privacy protection by the United States
Federal Government.
Revisions to This Policy
The Company reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our Internet Service Agreement
and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision,
amendment, or modification will be posted in accordance with the Internet Service Agreement.
We are not responsible for any typographical or translation error.
